<resources>
    <string name="app_name">House Genie</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="rent_vs_buy">Rent vs Buy</string>
    <string name="message">Message</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="mobno">Mobile No.</string>
    <string name="reg_no">Reg</string>
    <string name="buy_vs_rent_calculator">Buy vs Rent Calculator</string>
    <string name="rentvesting_calculator">Rent vs Rentvesting Calculator</string>
    <string name="house_value_description">Use this tool to calculate the returns from your existing house investment</string>
    <string name="buy_vs_rent_description">Use this tool to calculate whether it is profitable to rent a house for yourself or should you take a loan and buy instead</string>
    <string name="loan_details">Loan Details</string>
    <string name="buy_home_scenario">Enter details for home buy scenario</string>
    <string name="self_living_scenario">Enter details for self living scenario</string>
    <string name="input_down_payment">Down Payment Amount (including stamp duty etc.)</string>
    <string name="input_cash_payment">Purchase price (including stamp duty etc.)</string>
    <string name="input_maintenance">Annual Maintenance costs (tax, insurance, repairs etc.)</string>
    <string name="input_loan_principal">Loan Amount</string>
    <string name="buy_more_profitable">Buying a house is more profitable in this case since the cost of buying is less than cost of renting</string>
    <string name="rent_more_profitable">Renting a house is more profitable in this case since the cost of renting is less than cost of buying</string>

    <string name="house_more_profitable">Investing in house is more profitable in this case since the net returns are higher than other investment</string>
    <string name="other_more_profitable">Investing in house is less profitable in this case since the net returns are lower than other investment</string>

    <string name="cost_of_house_explanation">To understand how the cost of buying a house is calculated, consider a hypothetical scenario
        where you sell the house at the end of your loan period. The net cost of ownership is sum of emi and downpayment cost minus the sale price of house.
        Also, the tax saved from interest payments is also adjusted from the cost of EMI.
        \n\nSale price of house = Future value of house using the rate of appreciation
        \n\nCost of EMI = Future value of all the EMIs paid
        \n\nCost of down payment = Future value of the initial down payment
        \n\nInflation rate is used to calculate the future value of the costs.
    </string>
    <string name="disclaimer_notice">I have tried my best to be as accurate as possible in the financial calculations.
        However, there can be un-intentional bugs in the app. If you find any discrepancy or error please reach out at contact@harshmaurya.in
        \n\nPlease do not make important financial decisions solely on the basis of the results shown on this app.
        They are meant for illustrations purpose only.
        I will not take responsibility for any loss occurred due to usage of this app.
    </string>
    <string name="house_return_explanation">To calculate XIRR from the house investment, below factors are considered:
        \n\n- Expected annual appreciation of the house
        \n\n- Loan interest rate
        \n\n- Rental income
        \n\n- Tax savings from loan interest payments
        \n\nThe derivation of annualized return (XIRR) involves complex mathematical calculations.
    </string>
    <string name="investment_return_explanation">The rate of return from the other investment is already approximated using
        which the future value is calculated. This can be compared directly with the returns from house investment
    </string>
    <string name="cost_of_rent_explanation">Cost of rent is calculated by adding all the future values of rent payments over a reference period.
        \n\nCost of rent = Future value of all the rent payments
        \n\nInflation rate is used to calculate the future value of the costs.
    </string>
    <string name="home_vs_other_investment">Home vs Other Investment</string>
    <string name="home_vs_other_description">Use this tool to calculate to whether it is profitable to invest in a property as compared to other instrument</string>

    <string-array name="investment_types">
        <item>@string/savings_account</item>
        <item>@string/fixed_deposit</item>
        <item>@string/equity_fund</item>
        <item>@string/debt_fund</item>
        <item>@string/others</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="savings_account">Savings Account</string>
    <string name="fixed_deposit">Fixed Deposit</string>
    <string name="equity_fund">Equity Fund</string>
    <string name="debt_fund">Debt Fund</string>
    <string name="others">Others</string>
    <string name="copyright">By Harsh Maurya @SASHA BVN HANDMADE PRODUCTS LLP</string>
    <string name="rent_buy_intro">Are you living on rent? Do you want to check if it is profitable to continue in rent
    or buying a house is more beneficial?</string>
    <string name="rent_vesting_intro">Check if it is better to buy a house and live yourself in it, or do rent vesting instead
        (rent out your property and continue renting in another place yourself)</string>
    <string name="house_vs_others_into">Do you plan to invest in property but not sure if it will fetch better returns than
    other investment categories? Find out here</string>
    <string name="house_value_intro">Do you have an existing property and want to calculate the returns it has given till now?
    Check it out here</string>
    <string name="inflation_rate">Inflation rate (%)</string>
    <string name="india_marginal_tax">30</string>
    <string name="australia_marginal_tax">47</string>
    <string name="india_interest_cap">200000</string>

</resources>